Carson Mishoe

http://www.linkedin.com/in/carson-mishoe | https://carsonmishoe.com/ | carsonmishoe@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

I am currently attending South Puget Sound Community College (3.82 GPA), with 4 years of work experience. I am aspiring to learn Computer Science while working. With a wide array of jobs, I can put myself into a variety of roles. Frequently praised as efficient and hardworking by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.

SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, Java, Python, HTML5, CSS3, Java

Frameworks: ¡Query, Bootstrap, WordPress

Tools: NodeJS, SCSS, Git

EXPERIENCE

TheCoderSchool, Redwood City, CA

Coding Tutor, Dec 2021 - Present

- With knowledge of multiple languages such as JavaScript and Python I teach students Computer Science concepts in a way that's concise and easy to understand.
- Use time management and teaching skills to make sure the student is focused and able to learn complicated concepts in a reasonable amount of time.

BEST BUY, Olympia, WA

Geek Squad Agent, Sep 2019 - Jul 2021

- Consult and repair clients' computers with knowledge of solutions such as hardware or software.
- Led the sales floor driving a \$46 billion revenue using sales skills and great knowledge of the updated tech Best Buy has to offer.
- Designed and Implemented organization methods to efficiently test and resell returned products.

GREAT WOLF LODGE, Olympia, WA

Lifeguard, Aug 2017 - Aug 2019

- With CPR and Lifeguard training, I supervise pools of 100-200 guests remaining attentive and keeping all of them safe and satisfied.
- Use a wide knowledge of the company to answer questions and perform tasks to improve guest experiences.

EDUCATION

SOUTH PUGET SOUND COMMUNITY COLLEGE Olympia, WA

Associate in Arts (A.A.) General Candidate (Expected graduation Mar 2022)

- GPA: 3.82
- Relevant Coursework: Principles of Accounting, Introduction to Object Oriented Programming

PROJECTS

Discord Bot: I am creating a discord bot with my friend that aims to be a wiki of sorts for a video game using NodeJS and JavaScript. You can check out more at https://github.com/cmishoe72.

Personal Websites: I am creating my own website and other <u>HTML/CSS</u> websites with frameworks such as <u>Bootstrap</u> and others. Soon you may see some local business websites there! You can check out more at https://codepen.io/cmishoe72.